Okay, hello, hello.
All right, high team.
Thanks for joining today's Project Sing.
First agenda item is the Hackathon demo.
We'll discuss that.
The thing is, we need the prototype ready by Wednesday.
You get it right.
We need it immediately.
Raj, you'll handle the transcription pipeline.
And for the notion integration,
Priya will take care of it.
Second thing, let's finalize the candidate events for testing
by Friday.
Once that's done, we can prepare the minutes of meeting document.
Any blockers, we should discuss before wrapping up.
You guys have any more doubts or like what to discuss?
I need to more just hit me up.
All right, then.
Bye.
Okay.